How long did it take you to, like, get up and start moving regularly?
普通に起き上がって動けるまで
どれくらいかかったの？
I was, yo, you want to know something?
いや、マジな話していい？
What? You think I'm lying.
何？
絶対嘘だと思うじゃん
All right, cool. Which means you probably are.
はいはい
てことは多分嘘だな
Yo... I know how crazy it's going to sound.
いや、ヤバく聞こえるのは
わかってんだけど
Look, I was on my feet.
いいか、俺は自分で立ってたんだよ
I was on my feet probably, like, from the moment I could, like,
たぶん立てるようになった
瞬間から立ってた
from the moment I was alert and I just tried to get on my feet,
意識が戻った瞬間に
立とうとしてさ
I got on my feet. And I got into, I was going to say a fight, but damn near,
実際立ったんだよ。で、ケンカって
言いかけたけど、ほぼそれくらい
with the doctor for getting on my feet. He caught me on my feet.
立ったせいで医者と揉めてさ
立ってるとこ見つかって
You were in a coma for five days.
5日間昏睡してたのに
I'm like, yo, I thought I'd stand up. La, la, la.
俺は「立とうと思ってさ」とか
なんとか言ってたら
And, ni**a, he spanked me out.
あいつにシバかれたんだよ
He spanked you out?
シバかれた？
What did that mean? The doctor spanked you?
どういう意味？
医者にシバかれたの？
No, I got into it with the doctor
いや、医者と揉めたんだよ
because I was trying to get up on my feet
立ち上がろうとしてたから
and he was telling me to chill, like, you feel me?
落ち着けって言われてさ
He said he spanked you.
シバかれたって言ったぞ
You know when you're in the hospital,
病院だとさ
you got the f**king gown on.
あのガウン着てんじゃん
You see what he be thinking? You see what he be thinking?
こいつが何想像してるか
わかるだろ？
You see what he be thinking?
何想像してるかわかるよな？
He spanked you, bro.
ケツ叩かれたんだよ
Did you really remove a bullet out your neck?
首から弾を自分で
取り出したってマジ？
Yeah, while I was wide awoke.
ああ、意識ある状態でな
Because you didn't want to go back under anesthesia.
また麻酔で
眠りたくなかったから？
Yeah. You did it with a scalpel and numbing cream.
そう
メスと麻酔クリームでやったの？
I didn't do it, but the doctor did it and I was wide awoke
俺じゃねぇよ、医者がやった
俺は起きてただけ
and I'm like, nah, I'm not going to sleep.
「いや、寝ねぇよ」ってな
That changes the whole story.
それじゃ話が全然違うじゃん
I thought you was on some Rambo s**t.
ランボーみたいなこと
したのかと思ったわ